# **BORISLAV ALEKSANDROV**

Aberdeen AB25 1LE b.aleksandrov@rgu.ac.uk +44 7716 832 672



I have more than advanced work experience with all kinds and types of customers. I am very enthusiastic to start a new job and meet new people. I am a fast learner and a great teamworker, and a very positive person overall, so I can work with any system with all types of clients. I love making people happy and satisfied with resolutions, that is my motivation, to keep going and I am always ready and looking forward to learning something new.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Bar Staff**

Codona's, Aberdeen-September 2022 to January 2023,

I worked as a Bartender and Waiter staff in a busy and fast environment. I was able to learn and perform tasks in a rapid and effective way accordingly.

I was able to even work and adapt to the Christmas Village Fairs.

## **Customer Care Representative**

JustEat, Sitel Bulgaria, Work at Home - May 2021 to September 2022,

I was tasked with taking care of all type of customer queries, from problems with their order, to problems with their accounts. I encountered every kind of a situation, which can regard a customer and perfectly completed all of my work, giving me from maximum to almost perfect scores on my work quality scorecards. I had the amazing opportunity to work in a team of 12 people, together with a supervisor. We helped each other all of the time, staying in google meets throughout our shifts, socialized, helped, laughed, joked and even helped each other in case of frustration — overall heighten up the mood together. Working here, not only I learned to adapt fast, communicate with all kinds of people worldwide and complete tasks with my supervisor, but I also found a lot of friends with who I had the great opportunity to handout, laugh and even organize massive team buildings together.

There in terms of tasks I learned to talk with people and ensure them via phone or chat. Use the designed macros from my supervisor. Write daily emails and help customers resolve their cases satisfyingly. Be a mentor of new colleagues, befriend and teach them all the processes of working with customers.

This position taught me to work in a group and to listen, adapt, and complete my tasks in a way that is satisfying for me, my supervisor and most importantly – the customers.

# **Front Office Administrator and Receptionist**

Hotel Smartline Arena Mar, Thomas Cook - Varna March 2019 to April 2021

My position was consisted of taking care of all the reservations, payments, checkins and cheouts, fixing any problem that a hotel guest had, navigating all the documents trough each departament of the hotel, and everything that may occur in the meantime, When anyone had any problem in the hotel, they came to me, so i had to learn how to handle and resolve any problem a customer, or a colleague had trough my shifts. I had to work with a lot of documents, connected with reservations, abroad payments, emails, and many more.

In the meantime i had to make a daily check in and a check out every day, which included multitasking, managing payments, explaining to them the rules of the hotel and answering any questions they had for the hotel.

This position taught me how to handle any problem in any time, how to work with money more efficiently, how to talk and communicate with people from the whole world, and how to help anyone in need.

## Waiter/Barman

Hotel Melia Grand Hermitage - Varna January 2018 to December 2018

I worked as a waiter/bartender nightshifts only.

Had to make cocktails, by customer requests and by the menu.

Cleaned my workspot at the beginning of each shift and the end of it. Helped the hotel residents with any questions or requests they had.

Was able to handle any problem that occured in my shifts.

#### Waiter

Hotel Alegra Aurora Golden Sands - Varna February 2017 to November 2017

My position was as a waiter for a hotel restaurant.

Served and cleaned tables after every guest, wishing them a nice day upon leaving the restaurant. Washed and polished dishes. Took out any trash from leftovers.

Worked with a lot of people and learned how to cooperate in a teamwork environment.

I had to speak with foreign hotel guests and help them out with any directions or needs.

# **EDUCATION**

## **Robert Gordon Univercity, Aberdeen**

2019 - 2023

Currently studying final year for BSC Hons, Computer Science, Aberdeen

## GCSE or equivalent in Information Technologies, Mathematics and Computer Science

2013 - 2019

IELTS Certificate of 7.0 in academic English,

**B2** certificate in French

# **SKILLS**

Front Office, Customer Care Representing (16 months), Microsoft Excel (5 years), Microsoft Word (5 years), Cash Handling (6 years), Cleaning, Office Administration (2 years), Receptionist (2 years), Microsoft (5 years), Customer Service Skills (6 years), Java Developer (4 years), Database handling (2 year), Programming languages such as: Java(5 years), Python(2 years), CSS, C++, Javascript, HTML and JSON – each for a year overall, excellent Mathematician.